ratracerebellion.com 2009-05-22

# Rat Race Rebellion - Screened work at home job leads from Staffcentrix

As seen in/on:

Screened Work at Home Hirers by Field  
  
Accounting & Financial Jobs  
  
Administrative & Clerical Jobs  
  
Artistic Jobs  
  
Call Center & Customer Service Jobs  
  
Consultant / Expert Jobs  
  
Education & Tutoring Jobs  
  
Engineering Jobs  
  
Healthcare & Medical Jobs  
  
Human Resources Jobs  
  
Job Search Lists & Boards  
  
Legal Jobs  
  
Medical Transcription & Coding Jobs  
  
Miscellaneous Job Categories  
  
Mystery Shopping Jobs  
  
Non-Profit Jobs  
  
Notary Jobs  
  
Surveys - Paid  
  
Technical & Web Jobs  
  
Transcription (non-medical) Jobs  
  
Translation & Linguistic Jobs  
  
Writing & Editing Jobs  

Work At Home Resources  
Google Your Way to Telework Job Leads  
  
Tips for Spotting Scams  
  
Home-Based Careers by Niche  
  
Telework/Telecommute Resources  
  
Business Ownership Resources  
  
Freelance/Contractor Resources  

Bonus Resources  
Freebies  
  
Family & Children  
  
Lifestyle & Society  
  
Aging Workforce / Boomers  
  
Military Spouses  
  
People with Disabilities  
  
The Environment  

About Us

Who are Chris & Mike?  
\- Personal  
\- Professional  
  
For the Media  

In the News  
  
Speaking  
  
Contact Us  
  
Privacy Policy  

We're the Virtual Career Advisors for Military.com   
Be sure to [read our column](http://www.military.com/advisors)!  

|    
**Privacy Policy  
**  
At Staffcentrix we recognize that privacy is important, and we are committed to safeguarding your information when you are visiting any of our sites (Staffcentrix.com, RatRaceRebellion.com, 2SecondCommute.com, MSVAS.com, WAHBoom.com).   
    
This Privacy Policy discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this site.   
    
**Personal Information**   
This site gathers personal information when you register for any service we are offering or when you voluntarily provide such information. Your personal information is never shared with third parties; however, it may be included among any statistics we generate regarding this site. That is, you will be “just a number” among many if we do share information with third parties, i.e., the Rat Race Rebellion has 10,000 members (and you may be one of them)!   
    
**Log Files / Statistics Trackers**  
Like the majority of websites, we do track and record information when you visit our website. Data collected and recorded includes the referring URL (where you clicked on a link to arrive here), IP address, browser type, country, platform type, type of domain (network, commercial, military, etc.), and date and time. This data does not link to personally identifiable information and is used, in the aggregate, to help us track the areas of greatest interest, responses to publications outreach, and other details that help us make this site as relevant as possible to our visitors.   
    
**Newsletters**  
When a person subscribes to one of our email newsletters (distributed via yourmailinglistprovider.com) we ask for an email address (required) and other optional information. Subscribers may opt-out of these communications at any time by using the “unsubscribe” feature that is included in every communication.   
    
**Cookies**  
This site does not use cookies (a piece of code that is placed on a user’s computer and tied to information about the user) except in instances when the user has entered a password to access information that is password-protected.   
    
Advertiser Cookies  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).  
    
[Click here](http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=2) for a tutorial on cookie removal.   
   
**Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. Staffcentrix is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of those sites. We encourage you to be aware of when you leave our site and recommend that you refer to other sites' privacy policies for more information.   
    
**Advertisers**  
This site is supported, in whole or in part, by advertisements from outside companies. As noted above, these ads may contain cookies set by the advertiser, for their own purposes, and we do not have access to or control of the information they gather.   
    
**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: cdurst (AT) staffcentrix.com.  
  
The contents of this site are the property of Staffcentrix, LLC  
© 1999-2008. [Staffcentrix, LLC](http://www.staffcentrix.com/).  All rights reserved.
